Hello, it's
nice to meet you.
Hello, Hair Grand.
Hello, Mr. Tak Box. Hello,
Mr. Then, hello.
Ah, I'm
Jihwa.
Oh, I
should have turned on the broadcast yesterday, but
oh, I
just used a shortcut.
Now, 1 is over, and
when I arrived, it was already past 8,
so I should have finished less, but in fact, I just kept
repeating the broadcast and going
until the end of the week and next weekend. It
seems to be the peak season now. It's like an
ice castle.
There were too many customers, so there weren't
any. In the process, people who were driving outside. Yeah, after work, after everyone else was finished, they came and said, "I'll eat in front of you, Jirang and Ori." After eating, around 9:10, I went into the KakaoTalk chatroom and saw that today's broadcast was Silk.
Oh, that's right.
Today's tool was like, how did you feel? The amount
of echo for this big up
was a little bit turned on, but I
don't know about the all-new one. I raised it a little for now. I
lowered the price of 4 quarantine books a little.
5. The echo thing was
a little bit on, so I went to the side and wrote it.
This is
simple until now.
First of all, adults
curling. Hello, thank you.
8 sized ez.
It seems like it's a bit much. I
raised it slightly.
Yes, that's why I was a bit out of it. I was
out of it yesterday,
but if you look at it, it was good, but today, it rained almost
all day and then stopped and came and
went, but if you do this, the
sheep can't go outside when it rains.
Yes, I
raised them and I won't give them liquid manure.
If there are no bones, they
lose silver. It's not okay to just get hit,
but what kind of
animal can't get hit by a wild animal?
In the past, the sound was beam, but they
said it was okay. They say things like that.
These days, customers or people
worry about getting hit by it, and
my grandmother said that it was the same when I raised cows last year,
and now it's the
same. It's all like that during the day, so what if it rains and what if it gets hit by a butterfly? They worry a lot like this. Also, yes, originally, under a tree, they look down on them or something, but when they fall, where is the trust?
People like this, and in that respect, are
related to that aspect, and if they're
not in good health and have a cold right now, and even
if there are individuals who have been around for years, they should be able to do it
five times with the endless number of strong individuals, and only the four
should be together.
Anyway, since we're not managing it that way here anymore,
if they
miss it, it seems like they've caught a lot of colds.
That's probably because they don't get it normally, right? If a beagle got it in the past, I do
n't think it would get better if you just beam it again, but if they get it only once and then
get it once, they're satisfied.
So, when it rains, it's like you.
I see typos, and the
biggest content that customers enjoy here is the
land. They take
pictures with the goats,
eat some food, and run around
a bit. When
that doesn't work, feed
sales go down significantly, and volume 1
sells out, and there aren't many customers.
Yesterday, I was completely out of my mind.
9. While
thinking about it,
as an employee,
there are things to think about, but
our ranch is far from the peak
tourist season,
so we still have nothing to do.  It's
not that there's anything different after breaking the 2nd row, but it's not that there's anything different. People who look forward to that one-season business,
especially during the peak season, the
weather is very
warm inside for 1 day and 2 weeks. I thought it was a bit like a prayer meta. So, when that time comes, I hold on again and say, "Please give me good weather again."
There's not much I can do on my own. I can't
overcome RC bad things with force.
What the hell, Mr. Han Na-rae, nice to meet you.
Hello, father.
Just now, the pig was outside in the distance. The
Pazka is still standing and
screaming. I gave you a special shout. Hong Bo-seok will be
02. Top, etc. Do you have navigation?
02. I wonder
if the
button Mr. Mo is a little more serious. I'll
take a look. The shiitake
mushrooms will probably be
benign. I do
n't know for sure. The shiitake mushrooms are not toxic at all. First of all, as
you all know better than anyone else, if
there's a wild mushroom that isn't a pack,
which one of them is edible for humans
?
Ah, when I went inside and there was a mushroom and I
didn't know what it was, I
ate it.  I think you should think about the probability of it being okay.
First of all,
rather than saying that there is nothing without a cap, there are far fewer
mushrooms that people eat without causing serious harm
than mushrooms that do.
Or, as
you all know,
among them, the ones that people
eat the most are 4. If you think about whether they actually live by sitting down, you can think of
this plant as being the same.
Strictly speaking, mushrooms, of course, have the same
greeting, right?
Ahhh,
the waist and the calf are different. They are related to each other.
Nevertheless, plants do not have properties because they are plants. The
reason plants are toxic is because
animals can't run around kicking them,
dousing them with water, or biting them. They
can't defend themselves in that way. They have roots, so they
have them.
Come on, it's the same. Mushrooms
have various toxic properties for self-defense, just like a
friend. They
have a defense mechanism like a baby. They
are rooted and
can't resist being eaten by bears. And strictly speaking,
Speaking of mushrooms,
the fruit of the mycelium is
not the body of the mushroom.
Rather than saying that it has given up on being peeled,
should we say that it is not the main body?
For example, pine mushrooms also go into a joint like this, and
where do they
come out?
What is it called? Through that, they
turn on the state of the mushroom gift and profit.
If you do an octaster job,
things will not go well there, but then pine mushrooms
will grow as fruits.
Mushrooms are ultimately fruits that do not reveal their spores to spread their seeds
like this when they hit the blue.
So,
if you cheer on oyster mushrooms there, they will ripen and grow more.
If we let them grow further in the state we eat them, they will
spread out tremendously.
Perhaps that's why the oyster mushroom's typo bursts and
then you should look at
it. Or you shouldn't touch it carelessly.
Then, if you scratch and produce too many, and
if we inhale the Q card in the air through our nose, it can grow like our hand,
so it
can be very dangerous because it can cause a
fungal infection.  It's the same
because it can happen, so I
know that you have to be careful. For the
same reason, it's less than
9 kinds of baby mushrooms. The king of the seeds and I carry books, so it's like a flower, like a plant, and it's possible to defend yourself. Also, as far as I remember, Tathagata has a body that can be destroyed. There's one person, Chaga mushrooms, and some kinds of mushrooms are medicinal mushrooms.
* They have a lot of thoughts.
In fact, among foreign cases, it will improve. A
woman with a few children may
have had diabetes. Usually, these
various complications come out for the third time.
People with adult diseases and company diseases are
more vulnerable to various types of poisons. So,
for health reasons, Chaga mushroom powder is
widely available. Powder is
actually sold a lot in wire stores and such. I
went to all of them and ate the powder through chemicals. At the
end of my 10th year, I put 3g of Chaga
mushrooms in my mouth and
ate it. There
were also cases like this with voices. Just because it's an
edible mushroom, it doesn't mean it's safe.
But the plants we
eat are the same.
The species that humans eat are also narrow and simple. If you
look at the whole thing,  Here, we can go out and
eat most living animals, but
among grains, the only thing we can't
eat is raw wood. Compared to the new plants that animals can eat, it
's extremely rare. But plants are their
opposite. Just like animals go out and
eat grass, if you eat that, you'll get a
stomachache. There are virtually no
things we can eat when we go out, and
furthermore, it's absurd to
just eat it. If we don't go through the next process, like boiling it in middle school, peeling it, drying it, etc., there's almost nothing we can eat right away.
Most of the things we eat are wild
species that have
gone through a tremendous process of modification to neutralize their toxicity.
Despite the neutralization of toxicity,
there are still various properties of this wood and this wood, and they
can have adverse effects, so it's best to
avoid them if possible and handle them safely
before eating them.
In that sense, mushrooms can also be considered persecution.
4. 5.
Then, if a baby is allergic to chlorine in a swimming pool, what logo
it is,
it's all right.
Should I go to a general hospital and get armor? If
it doesn't hurt, there should
n't be 4, right? GP. Eat
well, drink plenty of water, eat well, eat salt, and the more you
know, the more you shouldn't get sick. If you're already paying attention, don't
do it. If you have
severe abdominal pain, and the theory is
Aulos, Ni Amon,
then Mr.
Ara, I got a
checkup and criticized
heaven. I sucked LTE, but I fed 140g a day and added 70g of exposure. If you eat a lot of meat and eat little other things, it's silver. And now, this screen is heavenly with enough activity.
And the fear is that you can try the long ceiling. Are
there any external issues that continue to appear a lot or something?
Mike, Mike, 5, right? 10, 10,
Ah, this is the price of the open house next door. I
should have used Archer, but I accidentally raised it.
Oh, this is looking at the lead. There
might be some noise. Let's
adjust
it a little more. Now, even if I speak a little softer, the pie microphone will respond better. 4 If there's a lot of noise or something, please
let me know so I can adjust it a little more.
Hello, the person who ran inside. There's a
little
basic noise, but if it's
not too uncomfortable, please do it.
If you feel it's not good, I'll lower it a bit
and do that.
Anyway, I'll get an insulin test
done and try
reducing the amount of palm oil.
Of course, it's important to know how bad your overall diet is, and
it would be best to eat a lot of meat, reduce other foods, exercise a lot, and be active.
What do you think about 3
these days? I think it's very
unnecessary and
can be dangerous.
For Koreans, it goes
without saying that most of us, almost all of us, our country consumes the most seafood in the world.
And it's overwhelming. There's no country that
compares our seafood intake with ours,
but it's really just that our country eats the most seafood in the world.
Among those seafoods, we
don't eat the most fish. There are
many countries that eat more fish than us.
Japan eats more fish and shellfish than us, and
Spain also eats a lot of seafood.
There are several countries that eat more seafood than us, whether it's from the sea or canned seafood. Our country eats a lot of animals in those countries.
It's not because we eat a lot of shellfish and fish that we're number one.
Our country is the overwhelming leader in
seafood consumption because we consume a lot of seaweed.
There are no countries that eat dried seaweed and things like that like we do. Well,
if you think about it simply,
seaweed is called "sweet" in English, right? It's
called "seaweed". How can we say that? When
we see people eating seaweed and seaweed, at
least not now, but
these days, people ask, "Isn't it true that we export seaweed?"
And now, our food culture
has spread a lot, and until recently,
when they saw us eating seaweed, they
thought of it as similar to eating seaweed from the grass.
Those people lived a strong life.
In most cultures, eating seaweed
was considered nonsense. And I'm not
just talking about the West,
but Southeast Asia as well.
Wherever you go, with the card group, there are almost no
cultures that eat seaweed
except for a few specific countries like Korea and Japan. We
don't eat as much as we do, and Japan is
similar,
but
we eat seaweed.  So most people
grew up eating a lot of it when they were young.
Pregnant
women always crave seaweed after giving birth, right?
During the Joseon Dynasty, people living in remote areas
didn't have the same level of commerce as they do today, and it was
n't easy to obtain real seaweed in inland areas. The reason it wasn't easy to obtain seaweed was because seaweed
could be dried and transported for a very long time.
But
even then, it
was difficult to even dream of seafood. People living completely inland, except for
a little bit of salted seafood,
might have been deficient in iodine, so
when babies were born, they were
given megadoses of seaweed soup. I
think this had historical significance. It's been about
15 years since I read an article that said, "Most people in Korea have iodine overload,"
and it was reported that pregnant women and babies should not eat certain foods after giving birth.
I remember
back then, and it's the same now. They eat a lot of seaweed, and in the
old days, almost everyone in Korea would eat it while
eating school lunches. Men would also eat it while serving in the
military.  I would have written a college essay and other
essays, and I would
have eaten half of the company meal at work. In the company
meal, which is military food,
seaweed soup is served periodically and laver is served periodically.
Please do this. Even if you eat just a little bit, the
plan is that when you eat it as food, the
food is
extremely concentrated and contains a lot of iodine.
So, Koreans, who eat an incredible amount of iodine on a daily basis, to the extent that it is
difficult to find a precedent in the world, are
taking megadoses of
iodine. It is
basically
meaningless. It is meaningless.
Unless you have a physical examination and it is clearly revealed that you are iodine deficient, I think it can be done in that situation. I am
talking about
taking megadoses of iodine indiscriminately.
There are people who talk about iodine as if it is a panacea.
Yes, most people would have had a lot of iodine,
not a deficiency. In addition, adding more of this does
not have much meaning. And this time,
eating a lot of iodine unconditionally is
not good or bad. Wood.  If
you eat that much, your thyroid function
may actually decline, and if you have thyroid problems, it may even cause thyroid
problems. Even if you do all that, it's not a beneficial mineral. Considering all that, it's not that cheap, and of course, it's not so cheap that you can't eat it. There's no need to eat it anyway, but there's no reason to eat it when you can have a side dish. I
think it's really stupid. One
of our subscribers has had a
problem with it, and we sometimes
talk about it in detail.
Her husband has been
drinking alcohol since he was young, and his in-laws have always served
seaweed with every meal. They've always served seaweed as a side dish. When they
got tested, they said he had too much iodine.
What happened? Even without
taking iodine supplements,
eating a lot of seaweed
can lead to iodine deficiency in the body. It's
so abundant in seaweed.
I think it's ridiculous that Koreans, who eat a lot of seaweed, are so full of it that they're just pretending to buy it. Is there a
difference between bone oil and fat?  They
're not the same, but fat varies
slightly depending on where it comes from.
All fat is the same. If you
think about it that way, butter is also
fat, but
its name is different or
something. You can see it differently, right
? It's fat
from the same cow.
In that sense, the
nutrients can differ depending on where the fat is located.
Bone fat
literally comes from the bone marrow, so it's
a bit different from
general back fat or the fat attached to the outside of the grain that we eat a lot. Even if general fat isn't just fat from the bone marrow,
back fat, for example,
and kidney fat
all have slightly different nutrients. Kidney
fat is generally
much fuzzy and
has a high stearic acid content, so it's a bit
harder and
has a melting point, so it's
more stable. And
because it has a lot of stearic acid, it can help our bodies burn fat better.
Back fat is thin,
so it has the nutritional properties of beef fat that we generally think of.
Let's say it has it.
The fat that comes out of the belly
has a little more unsaturated fatty acids than that,
so it's a little softer. Even if we do that, we can talk about it now. The fat that
comes out of the belly has a
little more unsaturated fatty acids.
In the case of the outside, the pork belly fat was more
fatty than the initial fat, but it was also walking. I
think
I sold the answer, but I think it was small.
And the 4 fat
marbling and the big 6 fat on the outside are
also very different. I'm
not sure about the outside, but
in the case of horses, the back is the
most representative,
and the fat on the outside is young. For
example, if you buy something like Levi's, if you
buy the 4 sirloin, there's fat on the outside of the back, right?
But at that time, it was
literally a
lump of lean meat attached to the back, so the fat on the outside
is like this. When a cow
stands on its feet like this, the
back is like this. The pig
has a layer of fat like this.
So the fat ridge comes from the back, and
in the case of pigs, the pork belly fat is more
stable than the back fat.  I know.
That's not what we were
talking about. We weren't talking about horses. Horses are back fat, and
compared to the fat inside the muscles, even if horses couldn't be re-fed,
the omega-6b is much
higher in fat with large marbling. Back fat can't be compared to omega-3, and it's
a bit like this.
Depending on where the fat is, the
nutritional content tends to be quite different. I do
n't like anchovies, but I wonder if they
became 3g of delusional fish during the drying and storage process. I
think it would be lenient to assume that they became 44.
And they're not just dried; they
're boiled. They're not
caught alive after boiling and
gently dried. They're boiled once and
then dried. And when they're boiled, they're
piled up in a plastic tray.
Yes, if you think about it that way, it's a bit like that.
Not all mushrooms are toxic or anything. Now, mushrooms
can be thought of similarly to plants, and
there are some types of mushrooms that are somewhat toxic.
Hello, Evergreen.
Um, it's
obvious that snacking
is not good if you keep eating them.
It's like eating the young while eating the sex organs.  That kid, what do you eat in between meals?
This is not good.
People who are on keto and
those who run popular restaurants know this, right? It's
also something that Jason Hug has made a lot of publicity about.
Why do you eat when you eat? You
eat breakfast, and you eat 30 meals a day, like eating breakfast, and
then you eat all at once, so you get a snack. You play soccer once, so you get a snack. You eat in between, eat, eat, eat. At night, you eat lunch, and then you eat again. You
eat before dinner because you're hungry. You go to bed and
eat after you eat. You eat right up until bedtime, and you eat as soon as you open your eyes in the morning.
This is like being cruel. Especially when you hear people say they've gained some weight, they say that if you eat three meals, you eat three meals. Eating consistently in between isn't really good. And eating well first is important. Eating well means eating
enough protein. If you eat enough protein,
there's media synthesis, but protein is 1. The
protein I'm
talking about here is mostly theta-stable.
I don't eat beans or anything like that,
so if you eat Jeon Dong-su protein,  Basically, it
contains a lot of nutrients that help us spend the day more energetically, from various amino acids and B vitamins to minerals.
When we eat protein for the first time, the
body absorbs it best and rebuilds the muscles
once more, so it
can cause match synthesis. So, the
most optimized thing is to
eat the first meal well. Now, every day
given that day, when we are given the opportunity to
cause maxell synthesis, it
becomes a Merry Merry Flash. The opportunity is to
find and make the best use of that opportunity.
So, eat well and
you will have the
energy to spend the day again. In
that sense, it would be
good to eat well and reduce snacks a bit.
Speaking of casual, I thought of something. I heard that Japan is the
first to release goats at the end of the day. Is it okay to
give seafood as a gift? I saw that it is good for the body to
stand up enough.
Can I eat it carefully for a moment? Just be
careful for a moment. The word 1 day is a bit
ambiguous. So,
it is actually safer right after peeling.
Strictly speaking, if we consider the risk, it's
safer immediately after the release, and
after returning to the US. Because Japan
occasionally releases some to our country, if the ocean current
exerts a force, it
goes this way, and
when we say our country is here and Japan is here,
number 1 is Fukushima,
right?
If it drops, it
didn't flow in like this. The ocean current flows like this, so it
circles Pyongyang and so on.
So,
I'll take a look at the phone now.
Oh, ah, now I'll call you.
But anyway, it has to come back like that, and it
takes a long time, so it's
safer right after the visit. We'll have
to see what happens after returning.
Hello, MJ P. Hello, Mr. Wikki.
4. And then, if we look at it, it's
actually dangerous. The dust
will come out numerically. We'll have to
look at that and make a judgment.
They constantly test for radiation in the ocean, and even seafood, so
yes, we have to be careful while eating. If they
test it, it
's really P4, and it's all
rising steadily in the ocean. There's
a lot of it.  If we do that, we'll have to do something,
but I
don't think it'll be to that extent.
At least not until this time.
But I think it's a matter of time.
Yes, if we don't do something, I
think we'll soon not be able to eat seafood anyway. We've poured so much pollutants into the ocean. The
amount of pollutants we've poured into the ocean is beyond imagination.
This is the
recent Japanese nuclear power plant explosion,
and our relationship with Japan is not
good, and since they
keep releasing a lot of pollutants, it's
become 20, so
there are many people who think that Japan is interfering with the marine ecosystem with contaminated water from the nuclear power plant. [Music] It seems that many
people think that it'll be okay if Japan does it, but they've
already
released a huge
amount. The explosion in Japan can be dismissed as just one of many. And it
seems like there's a lot of morality in the sea near our country. There's a history of martial arts in the West Sea, and
Japan is
not only in calligraphy, but also
in the Atlantic Ocean and the Pacific Ocean.  They dumped it all over the place.
New Zealand and Australia also
closed their feet on their own land. It's
low. There's
no need to say anything about it.
From the middle of the country to the Bouquet area and the
sea outside of Britain, there are
dozens of places with radioactive waste.
After all the wars,
there are mustard, prickly things, and biochemical weapons for war. They
all threw it all away. It's low.
Major Won is the finishing touch. The
Soviet Union doesn't even know how much they threw away. The Soviet Union is like most other
countries, so
these are
four unscrupulous companies that
illegally dumped food and chemicals into the river and
secretly closed them all. It's
a bit
like we saw in the movie The Host. In the movie The Host,
a certain company
illegally dumped formaldehyde and other substances into the Han River, and
it
came back as a monster.
So, the fact that the four companies discharged it in that way is
not very clear, but most of the things that the country did are
recorded.  That's the argument.
So now the US dumped
radioactive waste in dozens of places,
hundreds of weapons.
Europe dumped dozens and hundreds of them.
Where and how much was dumped? It
's all recorded, but the funny thing is, the Soviet Union
doesn't have that well.
But for some reason, it seems obvious.
For that reason, the
Soviet Union dumped a lot in the Arctic Ocean. They
made so much
money that they couldn't even afford to eat c tongs. Now, that's probably because of the Soviet
Union and those guys.
Even without that, the reason
we hunt whales and eat large animals in the ocean in the first place is because there are
no more phones on land.
From that perspective,
when the Eskimos went to the land and became extinct, the
people who lived in the polar regions of the Arctic
hunted large whales and ate dogs to use the remaining megaphones of the ocean.
Of course, the Ks are the top predators.
Even if they're not top predators,
they
eat things like krill, right? They're very small, but
even so, they consume a
lot of everything, and
whether there's a top predator or a
megaphone son who eats too much, it's bound to be
relatively
polluted, and since they
pour it all in with food and sound, the sub-
character has a lot of space. If you
look at the square map that we gathered earlier, it looks wide, but in fact, because
the staff wrote a crap post, it's in a very narrow place, so I
wrote it like this.
Of course, all that was poured in was
n't just received and released without permission, but if it was, it's already
reflected in the sea. It's lazy. Analyze the island. It's in the sea now. It's reflected, so
we tested it and it's
okay. It doesn't matter,
but even then, when I threw it away,
it wasn't just big. It wasn't an illegal tour, but it kept
going through the concrete barrel.
There's a drum, right? I put it in the drum, like the iron drum that I use to store oil. It's a
monster, so I put something like this
in there and poured concrete
and cement.  After pouring it and
letting it harden, they put it on the ground and then, when they didn't like it, they
threw it into the sea.
But this was done in its own way back then,
after pouring cement and putting in the drums
and all that, they
measured the normal state from outside and
stuff. The sealers, they said,
had gas masks and all that protective gear,
like the people who cleaned up Chernobyl before the prologue.
After they finished all that work, they sealed it and
measured the radioactivity there and said, "Oh,
no, no radioactivity." Then, they
threw it all into the sea and
dumped it all. The
problem was that after
10 years, it started to
corrode.
Ha Tae-kyung said, "Of course, but
at the time, they probably didn't think about it that way. As it
corroded, it slowly leaked out. The
massive amount of radioactive waste that was scattered back then, and
then World War II, we
had two world wars, right? We went
through major political strife like the World Wars, and back
then, from ginger to fire, the boss
didn't teach water and fire."  Five
were created, but the country
couldn't do everything, and then they would pop up again. It was
really terrible back then. It
wasn't a situation where you could just casually fight a war, so they produced and manufactured biochemical weapons in huge
quantities.
After all 4 were over, you
had to choose between the 5. Why did they throw it in the rice? At
the time, people in
Japan also received it in that sense,
and I know that Japan had three boring places.
Regarding radiation,
ah, and this radiation does
n't necessarily come from islands of happiness or things like that,
or it doesn't only come from nuclear reactors. There's also
a lot of medical radioactive waste.
New Zealand, even though they
didn't develop nuclear weapons,
dumped it all into the ocean. It's the same in Switzerland and
other places. Even without developing nuclear weapons,
medical terms for releasing people
appear, and it
appears in the future section,
so it's incredibly similar. It's swollen and high, and
now Japan has already done that, and
there's one thing they dumped in the West Sea. I
don't know how Japan is sealing it or dumping it. I
don't know the current situation.
North Korea.  They dumped it in the Liaodong Peninsula, a little bit between North Korea and China, on the
Liaodong side.
Now, I
can see those things. If they start bringing them out, I
think that might be a bigger problem. Well,
Japan, Fukushima, of course, compared
to what happened at that time, it's
much bigger. A
huge, large nuclear reactor
completely collapsed and everything, so
I don't know the exact amount in terms of quantity,
but it's not just Japan's problem. Just because
Japan doesn't do that doesn't mean
we can continue to eat seafood and there
are no problems.
Hello, Sinabro. Yes, if you
think about it that way, it's scary. Oh,
yes, there is something like that. Regarding Irue,
there's a channel that I introduced to you when I introduced the Park video of Price Toss before, right? It's
called Atlas Pro.
There's a video that Atlas Pro filmed.
I watch it there and stuff. I
'll show you the thumbnail of the video.
This is the video. Ocean Potion on a true scale.
How much are we
pouring in?  G20 is
coming out well.
Yes, it would be better if we looked at it together and explained it,
but then the video is always cut off
because of copyright and
things like 4 pesticides
and ego gas Dong yap and then trash
Nasser alone is not easy. The
amount itself is a lot of trash.
Color and
then 1
chemical monsters and if you watch the video later, you will
get a rough idea of ​​how close the sea is. Yes, the number is right. It is a
problem to disclose it. It
is Japan, but
in Japan, it is
not okay to say that Japan is okay.
Japan, and we will have
to wait and see what happens after that.
How did people tan in the past? If you
look at the Bible, men or women who exposed their bodies would have been
stoned to death. I
don't know what people's perception was at the time or how it is written in the Bible about exposing their bodies.
In reality, if someone was stoned to death, I
don't know much about Gore now, but first of all, it hasn't been that long since the Bible was written. It's
only
been about 5,000 years. I think the history written in the Bible is
like that.
Looking at human history,
there are some difficult parts inferring the appearance of people in the past through the Bible. It
hasn't been that long since humans started wearing clothes. It's
literally like this. People wear
clothes. Other animals in this world
don't have clothes.
Only humans wear clothes,
but the history of wearing clothes is very
short.
So,
like all other animals, we
originally walked around naked.
Life Is it true that fatty foods
can cause old people's smell by producing a lot of fatty acids?
No, it's a lie. Give me a distance that can't be far.
Old Boy is good for the risk. Do you think that not eating olive oil and only
eating fatty acids is better for the risk? So, if you
increase the edible oil and change it to 1, it
will help the risk.
But if you don't eat it secretly and
just change it to oil,
change it to Yanggaeng, or eat Songjeong lard,
it will
be more effective. It's better
than edible oil.
Sikyung Nium. Any regular edible oil will do.
Public Rabbit Silver is canola 80 Ford
C Wooden.  If you eat sunflower oil, you'll get
an answer. It's too high in fat.
From the moment you hear about it, your stomach starts to hurt. It's
not good for you. You can't sleep well. Most
people feel bad after eating pizza.
Of course, it contains flour and gluten, but it's
because of the starting oil.
But there are so many rumors about starting oil. If you eat too
much, it
causes bloating, poor health, intestinal problems, diarrhea, and other problems.
In that regard, if you switch to olive oil, it's
a little better, but olive oil is still
animal fat. Especially
compared to the yin-yang path, there
are so many broadcasts about it. If you
change the yang energy through introduction, it will be more effective. They
say that smelt is bad for the body. What do you think? The only
basis for saying that smelt is bad for the body is
a survey.
I have videos, articles, and translated videos that show that it's absurd to draw any nutritional conclusions based on a survey. I have
uploaded a lot of videos on my blog and other places.
I think it would be good for you to look into those things little by little.
The name of the defendant's affiliation is ruminant
fat. It's the
beginning of human history and the fat of humans.  It's only been about
100 years since cooking oils were developed, but
most of the cooking oils we eat
aren't even 100 years old.
Soybean oil, for example, has only been around for about
60 years. Of course, in the past, we ate a limited amount of home oil, but the soybean oil we eat today, like Haepyo 0 oil, and the public names like that, have only been developed for about 60 years. Canola oil
was developed in the 1990s and 2000s.
Compared to those completely new oils that have only been around for about 20 years,
silver
has a name. And
the diseases that modern people think they get from eating soybean oil
didn't even exist in the past.
Before those bedding oils were developed, it makes no sense to think like that.
100g of Caesar is a lot.
If they want to eat more meat, it's better to give them more meat.
Even if you reduce the amount of chestnuts, reduce the amount of chestnuts, and
increase the amount of meat, don't worry about that.  You
don't have to use it. You could just reduce the amount of food and
lose weight by reducing the direction of shaking, but
if you want to eat more meat, it would
be okay to give more.
Salt. There's already a lot of salt on land.
Some animals that live in the sea and
humans get the same amount of salt from the sea.
Anyway, the vast majority of creatures that live on land get
salt from the land. What about salt?
Yes, in the past, they ate it because of cancer.
In the Himalayas, they mined it in Utah, and in Redmond, they mined it because it was in another
state. They say that salt comes from Lake Death Valley and the Andes, and they say that salt comes from three private appeals. Of course, the price could go up. But salt was traditionally expensive. In the past, salt was regulated by the government, and the
government monopolized it
and
had all the rights to sell it. They
gave salt monthly,
and that's not a good thing, but now we
can change that. If the ocean becomes too
polluted and shrinks, and it becomes difficult for
us to do anything with it anymore,
or if refining technology
develops to that extent,
is it bad for the liver to produce a lot of gas when eating raw vegetables?
Well, rather than a bad liver,
vegetables are also good.  Vegetables are a bit
different, but I think it's best to think about the process of germs that are the most important. I think it's
better to think about it as the biggest problem. The problem is that the lines are too processed, whether it's bacteria or mold, so when you
eat vegetables, the islands there or sulfur compounds that cause other gases make you feel stuffy. I heard that consuming a variety of new fruits that you've never tried before
can increase the diversity of gut microbes. What are your
thoughts on this?
Oh, well, maybe it's
just that.
These are products. So, just because gut microbes
diversify doesn't mean it's necessarily good.
If someone claims that, I'll
look up the reference, but I'm
not really interested, so I don't really want to look it up.
If they do, I'll just say, "Oh, that's right." It's a
game where black people eat well and live well, and it's
polluted to the point where they have to eat money. The reason why Korea
can't live well is because
Western countries
produced incredibly cheap corn by digging the ground with oil, and then they just
spread it around for free.
It's a resource from the past.  Oil is a future resource,
so they
burn topsoil to make a lot of cheap grains that
can't be consumed domestically,
so of course the government subsidizes those farmers.
Otherwise, the
price would plummet. If the
government gives everything now and then buys it and
pours it into Africa through trends and such, saying it's a good thing, then the
farmers who make a living by growing grains in Africa,
or the farmers who raise animals and
make a living,
or the farmers who process
food using local agricultural and livestock products,
all of those crafts will fail.
There are countries that give out huge amounts of grains for free, but they grow
small-scale, traditional methods
on their own land.
However, no matter how much they grow low-yield sorghum or
other crops, they
won't be competitive in price and
no one will want to buy them. Then,
all the farmers who were producing grains will be beaten up, and all the farmers who were producing livestock on their own land will be
beaten
up.  The food industry
will also collapse, and if the local
food industry 1 and 2 collapses,
the country will become unable to survive unless it continues to receive free public offerings first.
My BD is living well, but
Western countries are going in and destroying Africa.
First, countries like Britain and France are
going in and
destroying it. They are
enemies, and they are gathering together some tribes and turning them into a
distant country.
Then, they create something that is clearly drawn
like a straight line in front.
That's actually how
it is with confessions.
When dividing a country, they
go to the map and learn latitude and longitude and draw a line like
this.
Then, from here to E, land,
from here to D, land, let's eat like this.
We are used to it, but
since that tribe was born, they have been
enemies, so they go in five times
and kidnap, kill,
plunder, and burn everything.
Yes, yes, the Shadow people become one country and
fight among themselves.
That's how they approach this ruined country and
get free grain.  The originals
poured in and
destroyed the local food industry, and it
was really bad.
Hello,
Mr. Yoon. Hello,
what do you eat at the store? Besides the production ledger, I
eat tripe with beef intestines and beef tripe,
but other things are more difficult. What kind of perfume is there for heartburn? The most eaten is liver. As for the rest, I actually eat a lot of the
internal organs of cows and sheep, but I don't eat them
that much. I eat kidneys sometimes. Yes, it's not that often.
Ah, I used to eat bone marrow often,
and I don't think I've seen it recently. I
just chewed the
bones and stuff, and it's a bit long, but I used to buy Coles bone broth and scrape the insides out and eat it. 4. What is red merlot? I used to eat it recently, but I'm embarrassed. It's like galli.
So, I bought bony parts
like yellow merlot and red merlot, and I
ate them, but
not that much. I
think the only thing I can say I ate consistently was liver.
First of all, I'm  It was so expensive that I
bought it in a hurry. Ah,
the tripe is more expensive, right? I think
each store
has specific peptides, but it's difficult to
quantify the nutritional effects of the mech peptides.
Excluding that, the eunji has a lot more
iron than other parts.
And the shiitake mushrooms are
probably processed by the
red blood cells that have reached the end of their lifespan. So,
the iron is not overwhelmingly high.
Compared to regular lean meat, the sirloin has
a lot of vitamin B2 and riboflavin. It also has a lot of
copper. The tip of the nose has more of it,
but the tip of the nose has the same amount of vitamin B2 and riboflavin. If you
eat a lot of meat, you don't necessarily need to
get it through the sirloin.
There are things like that,
so I don't eat that much. The
tip of the nose has more of it, and the
liver and yolks have more of it. If you don't eat these things, you can
eat a lot of meat. Amen. Even if you eat a lot, you can't get a Peugeot knife.
There are, and
in that respect, I'm also praying for the right amount of time. Is
freckles or blemishes caused by nutritional deficiencies?
Cloudy, sun-exposed face, dewy, these two things
seem to be a lot, right? I'm
worried about this princess Karen.
I heard that your face needs to be exposed to sunlight. If you
gradually get fit, you
'll be fine. I
saw Haepyeong 3-pae Seoan and then continued to
apply Senkaku sunscreen. If you suddenly
get too much sun, you'll
get freckles, your face will tan, peel,
hurt, and burn. But if you
gradually increase your exposure to Happy 3, you'll
be much better.
Yes, for example, right now
is the time when the sunlight is strongest, right? At this time of the year,
suddenly going out for 12 weeks and
not getting fit normally is bad. If you get exposed for 30 minutes
or an hour like this, you'll get
a lot of burns and it's not good,
so from now on, I'll go through some light and go
out in the morning or evening when the sunlight is weaker rather than going out at lunchtime when the sunlight is strong.  It's
better to receive it,
and you can receive it gradually. You can receive it while wearing sunglasses. And if you
receive it while wearing sunglasses, freckles and such
will appear more easily. I don't know for
sure, but if you wear sunglasses, the eyes of the monster are like
that. So when we receive light through our eyes, it's like early redemption, or we have cells in our skin that detect light. So even if we close our eyes and wear an eye patch, when our skin is exposed to sunlight, or when our skin is exposed to a plate, or when the
light
leaks from the light over there, our
skin can perceive things like the
arch gold is still daytime, or it can
perceive that the sun has risen and it's daytime.
But
Jinhoon is the one who sees and receives such things much more powerfully than our skin.
Feeling the sunglasses, when we
eat a piece of cheese at a meeting, even if we go out,
now is the most powerful thing in our body.
What kind of situation do we have to
accept and use? 2. Is
it night or something like that? I thought about it a little like this.
And if you think about it like that, when your
eyes receive sunlight,
it orders your body to produce melanin.  Now that I've received sunlight through my eyes,
I recognize it
and it's giving orders to my skin to do the same. If you
look at the order,
4. With sunglasses on, isn't
the elan not coming out well? It's
not that it doesn't come out at all, but it's coming out less than when I was in it,
so my skin doesn't get tanned easily. If it's not normal, I think it's good, but my skin should get tanned, just enough to avoid damage. So, it's like a
white person who is almost completely transparent
suddenly gets exposed to a lot of sunlight in the equatorial region
without any protection and gets
criticized.
Of course, that
doesn't mean it's unconditionally a basic right, but anyway, it's
like I've suffered a lot of damage, and my ivory
stress is really bad, and my skin
is peeling off. Yes, it's
gradually receiving
that amount of damage, and my skin and tanning were happening, and melanin protects our body, so that wouldn't have happened. 4. If we keep going out and moving while wearing sunglasses, our skin does
n't get tanned well, and our
eyes can't tell if it's day or night for
9 minutes. It's like a Saint-Glace
feeling,
but bad things can
happen, so
it's better not to wear sunglasses or glasses. So
Glasses are very harmful to me. They
filter everything through the 122 lens of the bit light and send both.
Of course,
there will be things that come in like this, but since it will
be external to the positive type, I try to
see the scenery as much as possible, and now I do it in the
morning when the sun is weak. It would
be good to gradually increase the time while receiving sunlight. If you
increase the time like that and
receive it again at lunchtime, this kind of
thing won't happen in the middle of the game.
Hello, 02.
When I was young, I
grew a lot of rapeseed flowers to make eco-friendly biodiesel, but
when I got stuck on that non-eco-friendly thing, I
feel like the camera market has grown tremendously. We
still make a lot of biodiesel. Even
if we make a lot of biodiesel from corn, it won't
work. We don't have that in our country. We don't produce that much grain ourselves. But if you go to the US or Europe, you can see that when you try to put oil in the state, it's written like this.
What percentage is it? 80%? 1st? 95%? It's
written like this. The higher the number, the
more expensive the oil price. The
lower the difference is.  Cheaper,
for example, if it's 85 or E85,
85% is gasoline extracted from real oil,
and the
remaining 15%
is biodiesel. It's like alcohol, a
fuel made from something like wood.
So now we're mixing it and using
it. In fact, even in the US, cheap oils are all mixed like this, and Europe is all mixed. And now, depending on the car, there are cars that can just use high-quality oil, and cars that can't, and things like that. So, in
our country, we spread it out and
don't put diesel in the car, so it's confusing.
4 Well, that's why it
's written on the car whether you can put in 80% of the profit you can put in or only 95%. When
you open the car, it's like this.
It's funny.
Producing
biodiesel, for
example, means making a road from corn and
using it as energy.
But the problem is that the oil that goes into
extracting oil
from the 3rd gen corn takes power, so let's
use it.  It's ridiculous. They
use more energy to
make small nuclear pods and
sell them cheaply, so
2. Green
You're physiological creamer swing. Oh, you just
finished a company dinner.
Oh, today is the day to celebrate the overlap. Should I
get samgyetang or baeksuk?
Since it was 70,000 won,
rather than samgyetang, it would
be better to have the same thing with a slightly larger chicken as the motto. It
hasn't been long.
But there are many choices on Sundays, and it's
3 o'clock on Sunday. Oh, I
wonder if that's why you came
late. Did you eat fruit on an empty stomach in the morning? Is that right? When you fast, at 1 o'clock, basically, it's good for us to extend our fasting period a little during the day. Most modern people eat late and wake up
in the morning and eat
fruit right away when their fasting period hasn't been long.
Now, it's bad because it
reduces the fasting period after eating a snack.
And even
if we eat, if we
eat food that stimulates insulin as little as possible, can we not break our fasting significantly?
Can we give insulin enough time to rest for a while?
But fruit only contains water and sugar, so when you
eat it, insulin is
released right away.
Our body needs to
maintain a proper balance between a state where insulin is released and a state where insulin is not released. This state of storage must be maintained for five years.
However, for most people, insulin resembles a dome. In the meantime,
putting fruit first on an empty stomach as
soon as you wake up is like eating sugar without any other nutrients, so there is no benefit to eating fruit. It is meaningless other than giving us calories. We can't fast without thinking about it, just by sleeping and sleeping. If we just extend the time a little more, there are many
benefits to
walking, but it's like eating fruit all at once without any benefit.
So, I just
ate a hearty meal with meat and rice.
There are areas and fields that come from there, and
there are various benefits that spring brings, but fruit is nothing like that.
It's useless. It only
has bad points and there is no lottery. If you
have a bad intestine, would it be better to eat raw vegetables?
Raw vegetables themselves  If you have a good stomach, it's
best to avoid it.
What kind of restaurant should I go to if gas is completely cured? It wo
n't help anymore, right? You'll need to manage it.
When you have a lot of gas, it's best to minimize plant-based foods.
If you eat a 10-free diet, it's simple, and it
has a lot of fiber,
or something that's easy for our bodies to
digest, or
something like white rice. Then,
fruit isn't that bad. It's better to eat something that's
a little too much, but
rather than something like Samejima, it's a little bit
l. The appearance and name don't really matter, but
sometimes, fruit
can be helpful if it's not written down. But the worst are
grains.
Next, leafy vegetables aren't very
good either. Gas, in particular, is
greatly affected by Hwaeom water.
Koreans
eat a lot of garlic and other things,
right? Because they eat so much garlic, there's a high possibility that sulfur-reducing bacteria have overproliferated due to the sulfur coming from that village. It's easy for most people to not do that now.
Many people also
eat kimchi often, so
in that sense,
vegetables are also 5.
Overall, all pia.  It would be more helpful, but
among them, if we have to be especially careful,
garlic with a lot of sulfur is the
most extreme, followed by onions, cabbage,
chives,
broccoli, cauliflower, and other
cruciferous vegetables.
It's good to know about these, and of course, it's good to answer the public contest. As for porous water and
such, white rice is an exception, and it's
best not to eat the rest. Seed
end
4. Now,
since you've reduced the amount of plant-based foods like meat, it's
good to eat meat in moderation.
In a situation where sulfur gas is produced a lot, even while
eating meat,
the amino acids in the meat can
extract the synovial membrane and apply it, which
can also produce gas.
If you have gas to the point where you have gas even after eating meat, it would be
better to go to the hospital and get treatment with antibiotics. If you feel
comfortable eating, you can
eat enough meat.
If you have severe gas to the point where you can't handle it, it's good to
moderate the amount of lean meat,
increase the amount of fat, and increase the amount of carbohydrates.
It's good to go in this way.
Next time, if you
reduce the amount of Czech meat you eat so that you can get enough nutrition,
increasing the amount of intestines will help.
Depending on the situation, you can also use nutritional supplements.
Hello, CJ. Right now, I'm
eating liver from Shindon Liver Center and Western
liver. I took a
perfume called "Petra" (Petra)
but now it's important.
Is there a way to relieve dry skin?
Eat enough fat
and use foam cleanser or something like that.
Don't use silver, just soap and
face.
If your skin is drier than it is now,
then when you wash your body,
use body wash, shampoo, or something like that. It's
delicious.
After that,
I think making something like Tanro night cream and applying it will help with the silver.
If Tanro night cream is too much trouble, you don't have to go all the way to Taro,
but just using sheep oil or acupuncture
right away would be okay. It might be a little
heavy, but are
one-day contact lenses okay?
Something is in your eyes now, and it doesn't go straight into the
flag, but through the flag, right?
Everything is the same.
Can't you get fat until you go to class?
Meal  It's a room where you can eat. There must
be some for sale. Do
bright glasses work? 4
Flight glasses that properly block the sun
are effective. I
think wearing those plate glasses is very good in situations where you might be exposed to bright light at night. The
downstream dive is expensive. The missing woman. I
think that kind of thinking is somewhat correct,
but the problem is that there are more
hip principles that go into making edibles that way. It's
just nonsense.
That's it. Hello. There's a
20-minute difference in real-time communication.
This is what I'm talking about now. I'll
try to answer each and every one of you.
If there's a lot to talk about, the
chat gets delayed and that happens. I'll
quickly move on. Then,
frozen meat, arch bridge, raw meat, grains,
vague resistance meats sold at E-Mart, king.
In the US, this kind of thing, this kind of thing?
Can you fix a nose and a prostitute?
When frozen,
what's so boring? Is there anything like this that's particularly boring?
4g of premium beef sold at E-Mart,
American beef, etc., they're all
frozen anyway. Most of them are just frozen. They're just
displayed at a meeting.  But,
knocking in the fridge makes the meat swell, right?
Pork belly, if the body
has a high linoleic fat ratio, it might also cause a
rise. I think eating
pork belly to increase the fat content can be a problem. Eating pork belly
too often
can delay treatment. Anyway, pork belly also
increases fat content. 2
Well, pork belly is really good,
but pork belly from factory-farmed pigs is
definitely worse.
I'm a dialysis patient, so would
n't it be bad if I ate meat? I have to
control my diet to preserve my remaining heart function as much as possible, and I
'm wondering if eating meat won't be a burden on my body. I'm not
sure what to do with my diet while on dialysis.
But, I don't necessarily recommend eating a lot of lean meat. I
recommend eating an appropriate amount of lean meat, but
in general,
there are parts that are more important than eating enough lean meat as an energy source. I don't
think one is more important than the other. What should I do now? But now that Khan is
protecting me, I think most people just
blindly eat a lot of meat, but if you
reduce the amount of meat you eat, you can also eat it.  You
can eat healthily by eating fat well without eating too much lean meat.
4 If your
kidney function has declined so much that you need dialysis,
rather than blindly trying various diets, I think it would be better to
contact them
or work with a doctor who knows a bit about this field and can
monitor you consistently.
Hello, Mr. Park Hyeon-gyu. Is there a big difference in nutritional composition between
Ogolgye and Dale Bantak, which have dark-colored fever meat and even bones?
Well, if you feed them similarly,
Ogolgye and Tagi, you
wouldn't feed them differently, right? Since they're the same person, I don't
think there'll be a big difference.
Kate 1 Cape 1 Leo White Rice,
then that's 500 micrograms.
How many eggs would be good to eat? If
you eat them every two days, it should be fine.
Meat, eggs, and fat are growing in this age.
If you eat 100g of liver every day, is it okay?
Not much.  I think I'll write in Korean. I
can get tested once in a while. I do
n't think it'll matter much.
Come outside and get some sunlight. Make sure you do
n't lack vitamin D. That's all you need to do now.
Don't eat all your vegetables. Do you eat too much for that body?
I
eat meat, fruit, and rice.
White rice makes insulin rise too much. White rice
doesn't keep your blood sugar up after insulin is released like this, so it's okay.
People who are sensitive to insulin have spikes once in a while. It
's not bad. It's not good if insulin isn't released too much either.
Insulin isn't necessarily a bad
hormone. It's a hormone that's released when it's fully cooked.
Insulin isn't a hormone that only lowers blood sugar. It
has many different functions. It's
good for a lover in a four-person room to come out once in a while.
If you're not healthy, I
'd like to hear your opinion.
Most of the time, I've been making suggestions and eating a lot of useless things, so I've been sick.
I
write about almost everything related to health
and made it into this video.
I've written videos and
articles on Channel 1 to help you understand the big picture, leaving out the really minor details.  I think it would be good to
visit my blog and
my YouTube channel and watch the videos once in a while.
When you eat steak,
is it absolutely not okay to
eat garlic powder or onion powder? I don't
think it's something that everyone should avoid. If you do
n't have any intestinal discomfort from eating it, then it
shouldn't be a big deal. If you continue to eat too much, you will eventually feel uncomfortable, but if you eat in moderation and you think you have no problems and are eating really well, then you don't have to worry too much. However, if your
intestines are not very good right now, and especially if you
eat foods that contain sulfur and
the gas is so bad that you feel it,
then you definitely need to refrain from eating until the problem is resolved. Is
cabbage bad for the body? It's
not that good.
Do you know what other effects you should pay attention to for varicose veins? For varicose
veins, if you eat a lot of protein,
exercise, and
take a little more taurine, it might
help a little more with the azelaic,
so I
wonder if that would be helpful. You could try taking
taurine as a supplement. You could also try
that.  You
can try it,
but basically,
eating a lot of milk, eating a lot of protein, and
exercising
will help. I
saw a survey in the past about when you start breastfeeding and discharge, but
Shakion is almost nothing, and it's been a long time since I
opened the reagent and didn't eat it while breastfeeding, but
after seeing it at that time, I do
n't know if it will come in when you start with Seolkyung Yuin formula milk, but
it's a work-type, so what do you think? Formula
milk isn't sterilized childcare,
it's a mixture of sterilizer and starting oil. Ah,
look at the ingredients of formula milk.
There's not a single formula milk that made a path to starting formula milk. There's not a single one. There really isn't a single one. They're all going back to school. Formula milk is just milk. In this world, the
previous percentage is not used as a food additive or
something like that, or it's
not used when making bread or things like that. There's
not a single case in the world where formula milk for babies is just given as is. After expressing milk, it's dried with hot air and spray-dried into powder.
Then, something is put in and it doesn't work, but
there's c.  100%
goes in.
What is it? It's better to save c extracted from seeds than to eat
it. And now, the punishment is a craze. Parents, you should
eat formula made with the sins of the parents.
Of course, you
ate it with your mother's breast milk. This is a
big deal. Ah, I
wonder if the linoleic acid that is excreted is fed to the baby, or if it really comes out and goes there as the name suggests, a carcinogen. Of course, that means
a lot of oleic acid goes there.
Linoleic acid escapes and
goes to the baby.
Hello, Mr. Hee.
What are the top 10 foods that are clear and increase omega pigments in the C semester?
There's olive oil and avocado oil. Then, lard and
duck fat, if you
eat them in excess, it will
greatly increase the 5-person Asics metaphor. It's
unnecessarily
dry, but is
it possible to use the real name when removing sunscreen when washing your
face? I'm not sure about using the real name when washing your face.
Sunscreen,
that inorganic sunscreen,
doesn't just come off with water?
It's better not to apply sunscreen in the first place.
4 Sunscreen
If possible, it's better to apply the next one.
If you have to apply it, use inorganic sunscreen. Is there anyone who brightens their skin tone? If you're talking about a way to make your skin white, you can probably get some sun exposure, but I do
n't really recommend Nego. Please
tell me all the fruits you can eat. I do
n't know what I can't have. Make sure to
make them
organic. Things like bananas are organic. I
eat almost all fruits except bananas. I
bought watermelon once recently and ate it. I
bought watermelon at a 30% discount at the supermarket and ate it.
Even if you buy bananas organically, you can buy a 13kg box. It's
almost the same price as eating regular bananas or bunches. I
thought that was about it.
Yes, well,
I once did some research on the
types and amounts of pesticides used in banana farming. I
mentioned this on a previous live broadcast, and
after studying it, I was
curious too, so I
looked it up. People
talk a lot about bananas, and
the reaction was, "Why do they have thick skins?"
Organic is complete.
So now I'm thinking, "Is that really true?"  So, after
looking into it, I found that it's somewhat
true, but that does
n't mean the abscess isn't trying to go to sleep.
There are so many types of pesticides used when growing bananas, and
many of them aren't tested for
pesticide residues. And then, in even more cases, the pesticides used in banana farming aren't registered in the first place, so there are a lot of cases where testing isn't done. So, I used to eat it as an application. How much protein is appropriate for waist?
I wrote about daily protein intake.
Um,
the title is "Oh,
this is my blog. I
wrote about calculating protein intake like this. I
keep thinking about it. I think it
would be good to go here and take a look. There's even a formula for
how much you should eat.
If you roughly match it to that and
eat it with that as a goal, it'll
be 100%. Is it because
children get tumors or leukemia
because of what they eat? Formula milk will
also play a role.
100%. I'm sure it will be fine, but
from the time I was appointed, my parents' English was
so bad that I wrote it and wore a suit.  Since the man was
n't in good condition, he must have already been doing it from there. He
bought and ate Star 2 MP supplements, but he felt
nauseous and
vomited. Is this a side effect of vitamins? Vitamin P supplements are generally not recommended. For example, they contain a lot of Vitan Bis premonitions, or the form of the second B6 is inactive, so it's also too much.
Try taking a lot of 10B Won Dota 2 Amen HCL. The shielding
absorption isn't that great, and
in many ways,
computers need BTL B to be cheap.
There are also cases where it's Balam, so I think it would be
better to just eat well, and if I'm lacking a specific vitamin B, I supplement only that vitamin B. I think that approach would be more effective.
Eat liver well,
eat meat well, and especially eggs. I
think that's the most basic and important.
What about mustard?
If you try to eat a lot of meat, you end up eating a lot of mustard. You
know mustard, right?
In that respect, it's not good. I
think it's definitely not a problem.
What's different about mustard? Compared to Art, how is it?  Han Kyung-
seok: I don't know much about reading or the specifics, but it's just that it seeps in little by little with spices. And now, unless you have any health complaints about it, I don't think you have much to worry about. Of course, the part is the eye.
If breast milk doesn't come out, what should I feed them?
Should I eat goat milk or colostrum? It's
designed for that. It
won't be easy to consistently feed goat milk or colostrum.
No, it's not, but the baby won't
come out. It's
probably not impossible for parents to raise a child
while eating properly, but it's
not completely impossible. If you're not in a
state where you can conceive, it's not something that can be fixed. Especially if you borrow the power of science and get pregnant or something like that,
there may be many people who don't come out, but if you talk about it one-sidedly,
if you
take good care of it, you'll have enough to keep it. If
it really doesn't come out,
and if not, even if breast milk is good, you can't eat it. There
may come a situation where you can't get anything done.
When you do this and that,  The Press Foundation
now offers a homemade formula based on raw cow's milk, made as similar as possible to mother's milk.
In
Korea, we've
run out of words to translate formula, so you can just make it yourself. We call it either powdered milk or breast
milk.
So, if you think that something that isn't breast milk is just powdered milk,
there's a way to make powdered milk yourself.
I've shared a beautiful recipe on another Persian website.
Raw
milk isn't raw milk, and goat
milk and cow's milk have different ingredients,
so the recipe varies depending on what's used.
They're based on raw milk,
but humans are alienated.
Just as hunting milk and game milk have different nutritional properties, human
milk
also differs from game milk or goat milk. You can't raise a human baby solely on cow's
milk or goat milk alone.
So, the best approach is to follow a recipe that's as close to powdered milk as possible
without harming it. The
powdered milk recipe from Press is also
trendy. Why
is that?
I think that's because
all the research on human milk has been done so far,
so there should be a reference.
Isn't that human milk?  They're
trying to make the same ingredients, but when they make it in Prussia,
we
don't have any ancestral records of what kind of fatty acid compositions people like the Eskimos, the Wen Tal
people, the villages with the infected Eugene Lee Zealand,
or the Masai in front of us had in their breast milk
at the time when Dr. Flex Flex was alive. So, among the modern mothers who are breastfeeding, we
take the breast milk of healthy people,
analyze it in the lab, and
make it as similar as possible.
And the breast milk that comes out of that is
higher in linoleic acid than cows or goats. But this
is somewhat natural. The
fatty acids that animals eat through food are literally
just like our bodies. The
reason they have
more linoleic acid is because
they are monogastric animals like us. And the animals that are left
behind, like cows, sheep, and goats, have
the ability to convert saturated fats into 3.
So even if they
eat a lot of grains,
linoleic acid doesn't get lost in the blood.
That's why traditional humans
just...  The linoleic acid
ratio will be higher than cow's milk, but as far as
I know, the ratio shown in the picture is
20%, which is the ratio we use as a reference.
So, the name 5-wipe is similar.
Technically,
this 20% means that our
bodies cannot produce omega-6 linoleic acid
directly.
That's why it's an essential fatty acid.
For example, we can produce saturated fatty acids like 8-mi-tae-san
directly.
Non-essential fatty acids can be
synthesized in our bodies in various ways.
Or,
even if they can't be produced, they are
not essential. In any case,
omega-6 linoleic acid has an animal
form called arachidonic acid, or
omega-3
linolenic acid
has an animal form called d-chain arachidonic acid. Our bodies definitely need
a small amount, but it's a very small amount. This is because
we can't produce it directly.
That means we
have to obtain it exclusively through food.
But
looking at examples from traditional groups,
20% of our bodies are essential.  To build up that
20%, how much would that be?
About 20% of it needs to be consumed through food,
but we're
not even talking about 20% of it. If we look at the data below, which we
extracted from the body fat of Americans,
the omega-6 fatty acids in the linoleic acid fatty acid
account for 20% of the calories in barley,
so that's about 10% of our fat.
I
made a video about this before, so I
think it would be good to watch it. It's about the history of food consumption,
so if you look at it like that, if you want to
give 20% of it through breast milk, our
bodies can't produce it directly, so it must have come
from food anyway.
But traditional groups couldn't eat that
much linoleic acid to give their babies through breast milk. They
couldn't eat it, and they didn't eat it. At that
time, there was no oil to begin with, and
after feeding animals a huge amount of seeds, they
didn't eat those animals, and they didn't have teeth, so
the way we raise pigs now is
really raw.  He's so cheap and
nutritious, and that's all.
It's possible because it's so cheap.
Before oil was developed so cheaply and in such large quantities,
you
couldn't even eat a lot of pork. Hands and grains are
much more expensive than that, so it goes
without saying that the party is expensive. The reason
former President Roh pledged to make it so that every household in the United States
could eat a chicken every weekend was because it was
expensive and
luxurious. That's why it was so popular back then. And the
reason we couldn't win an award for citing the fact that
20% of linoleic acid could be passed on to babies through breast milk
is because,
given the lifestyles of our traditional people,
even if the breast milk of healthy modern mothers is so high in linoleic acid for three months, it probably wasn't like that in the past.
Well, anyway, you can't make a formula based on that guess,
so you have to get it. Anyway, we have to have an AhnLab Porsche. If
we knew the
exact composition of the fatty acids in breast milk from Masai Mara or rental people, we could
use that as a reference. That would be the best.  Since
there is no such thing, they have
no choice but to make the formula using the breast milk of modern mothers as a reference.
That's why it's
easy to use 6-move sunflower seeds. It's
not like it goes through all the processes with a strong color that doesn't miss anything, but it
uses pressed sunflower seeds. I
think it's a better choice. There, it's
pressed. Zion is
sunflower seed oil among seed oils, but
even if it's
easy to apply, it's sunflower seeds now. We're folding our company's pieries and
things like that.
What do you think about constitution?
8 constitution is complete nonsense. I
don't want to complain in the living room for a while because I've been too polite.
It's nonsense.
If I think about constitution, the easiest way is to think about it. If
our country
went back 1,000 years, we would
all have to eat the same food next door, in front of the house, behind the house, and in our house. Because
we
live in the 21st century of the wealthy Republic of Korea,
oil is overflowing and cheap, and we
eat it everywhere.  You can eat
all the foods you've never heard of before, so
what system do we
share? What books do we share? Oh, executives say you
shouldn't eat what you shouldn't eat, and since you
said you shouldn't eat this last time, you have to
eat only those. The
fact that we can share this is because our stomachs are full right now, and we're living
so well because we're full. If you think about it, if you
go back a thousand years and
live on the Korean Peninsula,
everyone in the house in front, behind, next door,
has to eat the same food.
There, they all have the same constitution and ate it.
They like it, but they compare it because they're cheap. Does it smell
bad?
Wiping happiness isn't like that. Apples do
n't have nutritional value.
Yes, they're just sweet and
have calories, so we eat
them. And when eating in Korea,
it's more natural to eat seasonal apples. I
often watch live shows and feel
pressured to eat the stores I want to try. It
does
n't make sense to eat other bad foods because it's hard to eat internal organs.
Even if you can't eat internal organs, you can eat other foods.
Don't think of it as the latter, but rather the former. If
it comes out right away, isn't gold okay?
Vitamin B complex nutritional supplements are generally
not that good, but Aronamin Gold
has a low content, and I remember it
not being that bad because of its low content. Let's
look for the remaining ones. Namin
Gold Aronamin Gold.
And as far as I know, since it's a pro set, it
contains TTF D. Did the Ministry of
Food and Drug Safety approve?
The raw material is defective. Aronamin Gold tablets. Are there
two types now? The
one above is limited, and the one below is two
types.
And the plugin is also six in the fight.
This is a different weapon, but it
seems to have two types.
4.
Anyway, pro-salt amine gives vitamin B1
T KFD.
Riboflavin is
needed. Poisonous phosphate long.
Active vitamin B6. This time, 2bp. Danbi
pitching. Yo. Ha. Resume. As a punishment, Min
emp. Tan. BTL. Just after that.
Ascorbic acid,
vitamin C, tocopherol, vitamin
E.
Compared to other vitamin B complex supplements, this one only contains phytosterol, fatigue-fighting vitamins, and
B3, which is expensive, and no EVE, B7, or
B9.
It's in zero form. But on the other hand, it
contains pita in its active form, and rather than an active form, it
contains DFD. There
's also rib clubbing, and
this mg is not too much.
But it's
a bit ambiguous to say that this is not a bad tea. Since it
contains riboflavin as a supplement, it has effects that we generally
don't get through megadoses and
want.
Well, if you think about it that way, this is
not through plum in. When we play, the
effects that we can get when we take megadoses are like this. You have to take 200 mg or 400
mg to get them.
If you think about it that way, it's 2.5 mg.
There's no attack, so the amount is a bit small. Yes, yes, anyway, it led to a big one.
But this is all 2.5. Is this
right? Must-read rice.  2.1 I'm taking
Kaidrox, that's it, and
vitamin C and vitamin E
40mm, so 40 mg, and is
this
around 60 IU?
Or is the situation at 8:30? Uh,
it's a bit more than I want,
but there are too many additives.
What is Shiki Miter? The nose foam is
no longer the top media market. Loss's
cross 4b. The typo class clear
star. The liver magnesium colloid is
strangely continued. It's dry and red.
But our country's supplements are also a
problem. No, what supplements? The body,
first of all, why is color important? What is Tang
sex? I put it in and took it for the
first time. Our country
doesn't like the sun very much. Useless
colors, but when I come home, I always eat English. Jumong.
What does my color matter?
Uh,
vitamin B. Tel. He
can eat meat as much as a little bit of booger, so
yes, it doesn't really mean much.
In the towering description, it says that it helps with temple formation, but will it
help someone who has been declared fat? It can be helpful.
Terrin just ate it.  This may not solve all problems,
but it can help. There
could be many reasons why this isn't working, or it could be due to other
causes. It could be a vitamin
B1 deficiency, which is causing the class,
or it could be a lack of lysine, which is
preventing bile production. Or it could be a
weak phase, which is preventing absorption. There could
be many reasons.
Which is better to eat on a regular basis, rice or goat milk?
However,
since the conditions are not exactly the same, it's better to
consider price and the breeding environment and
consume the more reasonable one.
Soda is an animal, and if you eat it, you
offer a gift and send an official document. It's not that there aren't young companies.
Soda is not an animal, but a
pig. It's a monotreme animal, and
since it's monotreme, it's one.
When you do the unit, it goes around.
Like humans, animals with one stomach,
we only have one tooth. We only have one, and
ruminants like cows, sheep, goats, deer, etc. have a dog between their eyebrows.
Guys, now
to eat grass,
plants with cows means it's that difficult. It's
really easy.  No, it's a very difficult task to use his plants
as an energy source and protein,
so he has four positions, for example. The
four women have so many swallows, and
there are bacteria that hydrogenate saturated
fatty acids, such as dream linoleic acid, and change them
back into saturated fatty acids.
Now, this is possible. So, even if
they eat a lot of grains, the
saturated fatty acid content
doesn't increase. It seems that they often use dried
[ __ ] bones roasted in butter instead of beef bones. Is it okay to
make them all at once and
store them in the refrigerator? I wonder if the
condition will be good. There doesn't seem to be
much risk of 3-loss in the butter. It will be
fine. The 3-mono
fatty acids in butter and such can be a bit of a condition,
but they don't contain that much. It does
n't matter if you store them in the refrigerator or freezer. They
enjoy it, but I do
n't think it's 100% replacement with dried [ __ ] bones. I
briefly mentioned before that I wondered if it could be done, but if you
look at the calcium in bone marrow, you can see that
we just store the bone marrow.  When you eat bone
broth, you
don't eat the bones again,
right? Whether he learned how to make bone broth, he didn't eat all of the bones after getting them from the bones, but only the broth, the marrow, and the liver, and finished it off. Or, even if he didn't test the bones, he finished it off a little disappointingly.
Since dried [ __ ] eats the whole bone, the
calcium intake is too high compared to the amount of bone marrow, so you
can't eat that much.
So, even if you eat only 2g of bone, you've
already met your daily calcium intake,
and it's all gone. So,
in that sense, I don't
really want to go overboard with eating a lot of dried [ __ ] every day, and
there's something like that.
Five years is a bit much.
He's aiming for three
breast milk servings in five years.
[Music]
Adding olive oil instead of sunflower oil
could be a way, but now this is
the next French Commade formula. It
's a recipe that's been proven for decades. If you
change it to olive oil,
there's definitely a part that needs to be verified again. It will depend on what you're going to use the olive oil for.
If you have extra
virgin olive oil, it
contains a lot of pulp, which will definitely have a negative effect on a child's body. It
could actually be detrimental.
There are such aspects. How
many days can you tell if the raisins are growing? I
do it once a week on Saturdays at 8 o'clock. If you
eat it every day,
it's good to eat about 30g a day. You can
also eat 100g twice a week. Do you
consume this separately? We talked
a lot about iodine earlier. The
person who came to the iodine department
asked
about other fields, so I talked a lot about it.
Ask if you consume it separately. You should
eat 50g five days a week, but you
have to do it. Is
it okay to use Korean beef when cooking? I've
seen all the cooking oils. Are
there 3 for each person? Is
there still almost no 5 for coconut oil. Do you have any
plans to work live?
Archer doesn't mind Saturday or Sunday,
but I've been
doing it on Saturdays so far. Rather, Koreans
Okay, maybe back then, there was a survey about
whether it was better to do things on Saturdays or work.
Back then, there were a lot of Saturdays, so we
did it continuously on Saturdays. OK, it's been over a
year since then,
so I'll
post it again on the YouTube community to see which one you prefer between Saturdays only. If you vote, I
'll go with the one with more people. I
think we talked about this for about 10 minutes earlier. 4.
4. Now, since we've worked hard, if you
have any questions, please ask any
more questions until 10:05 and we'll wrap up the broadcast. There's
no bathtub for Mr. C to bathe in, so it's probably
difficult to see the salt station on a large scale.
What is this? Some people have seen some effects with just the light.
But it's
better to have a large body.
Hot water, especially a
wooden one, might be a good option. Since
this is a bathtub for lying down, if you
think it might take up a lot of space,
there's that too. I
should show you a video like this. You can bring a long,
barrel-shaped tub that
goes up and down, and you can use it to bathe now, but
Cold shower, cold bath,
I think it's okay for you guys too. I was going to
show you a selfie before, but my computer turned off and the broadcast was forced to stop, so I
couldn't show you, but this guy named Meta Bowling Mike, and I
've introduced him to you several times. Is he a person?
Yes, it's a comedy video.
There are four
stories about him. I can give you this kind of wind,
so how can I wish for a
hot red bean porridge show? Heo Yu,
kick it 2 times. 1 together. Behind the scenes.
Ya. Se ...  It
might be better not to eat even that, and it depends on your usual health. If your
intestines are really bad, should I try not eating it for a while?
[Music]
Omega 3 is necessary in small amounts.
Now, to resolve inflammation,
DHA is needed for which spring
can properly cause an inflammatory response.
Of course, other than that, jj double amount is
so important here and there, so talking about
work is important, and dj I can't see the eyes that are gathered.
No, it wo
n't be that deficient in a short period of time, so
if you feel uncomfortable in your stomach after eating street food, you
can try stopping it for a while. And you
don't have to get DHA through fish.
Oh, so you can eat brains.
Or if you
don't feed it 4, and eat pastured meat,
you probably
heard a lot about 3. I
don't know,
but if you
don't eat a lot of linoleic acid and only
eat real beef, lamb, and pastured meat, the
alpha-linolenic acid that comes from that can
also be a source of plant-based omega 3.
Exo-salt pouches, no more.  Ah, I
heard it's a
pancake, but isn't makgeolli good? What's good about makgeolli? It's
fermented rice, 1 liquor, and Yangsuri, a
low-quality
premium. Do you sleep well in summer or winter? I do
n't take cold showers every day. I wish I could do it every day. I can't do it every day, but I do it consistently in the summer. Cold showers in the winter,
but they have their own flavor. Everyone,
summer is fine, but somehow, that really killing feeling you get in the winter
doesn't happen in the summer.
Oh,
pregnant women are rising in history and the hospital
says, "You don't have to eat it." So, it doesn't mean you
don't have to take
folic acid. You don't have to take folic acid only as a supplement. History tells us that if you eat the liver and yolk, you can get enough if you eat the liver and yolk of animals that graze. Or if we don't take folic acid supplements in the form of laughter pills, we
all remember everything. We were born and were humans. We
really decided that we
could all be healthy and give birth without that, so people have lived until now.
Cold showers are less effective.
But you don't know if they're even effective for about a minute.
When people say that cold showers are good,
most of the research that supports this is this.
They were exposed to a lot for a very long time.
So, in the study
conducted in Berlin, the swimmers were
always strong, and they studied people who could barely tolerate it for more
than 30 minutes. The
effect is not that great.
The body needs to be slightly, really cold,
not just slightly cold, but really cold
and shivering to
be effective. In
my case, in just 1 minute, I
looked at it right away as soon as I turned off the water and told them to open it. I
already had a lot of reals
and my fever was boiling. I was really cold
every day and
shivering, and my body was
not moving well and stiff. I
don't recommend doing this every day, but
for now,
doing it that way is the best for the effect.
So, what kind of meat do you eat? Meat, lamb, I
'm still eating it.
4 Hanyang minced meat was really the best value, but
now I can't buy it anymore. It's sold out, so I
took it with me, but I
think the supplies were gone.
Then, if the
meat I'm going to eat next time is
n't sold out, I'll
buy a box of rib bones.  I think I'll eat it.
I want to try prime rib, but
even if it's too expensive, I'll
hold back tears and buy Uruguayan sirloin.
I want to sponsor a whole sirloin and try it
once. I'd like to do something like that when we have a
gathering. I'd like to have a gathering in August, but it's
peak season,
so I'm hesitating a bit.
August 20th would be good,
but what's
the outlook? It's a bit strange
to say that we'll have a gathering and have fun while everyone else is working hard.
There are so many customers these days, so I'm not sure if it'll be that crowded on the 20th, but
anyway,
I think it'd be better to skip August.
It would be okay on a weekday, but we
can't have a gathering on a weekday, so it's
fine to come to Pal, but
it's a gathering, but it's a
bit much to come in 4 and eat snakes and stuff all day, so it's
a bit much to have a gathering, and
no, after experiencing this yesterday, I
felt that way.
Until then,  Well, it
wasn't that busy. It
was just busy, busy, busy. Yes, I
really got a kick out of it yesterday. If
the situation like yesterday continues, especially on the weekend, it's
a bit difficult to be precise.
Compared to the words and reviews,
of course weekdays are more comfortable.
Since this is a tourist attraction, there are a lot more customers on the weekends. I
always have to wrap up slowly, but
it's 10:13. I
have to upload the experience after showering,
but I heard that the video
wasn't good. Is it true?
No, it's a lie. It's ridiculous. Do
n't avoid it to overcome stress in a short period of time.
Why are you talking about a short item?
How about lamb tail? Meat Friends
is 4,900 won per kilo, but lamb tail has
almost no meat. It's mostly fat and
collagen.
If you go on a weekday, it's better.
And you
can probably save more time. It would be
good to come on a weekday.
Mr. Gonggi
said he'd come at 23l.
Anyway, you can go almost anywhere on weekdays,
almost any time.  It's okay. I
'm always here anyway, and
brown fat is activated, which
helps with the search collected.
Rather than limiting it to just body fat reduction,
there are many other great benefits, such as increased basal metabolic rate, target activation, and so on.
We asked for this livestock relationship, so
there is feed, and coincidentally, it's between the trading fields.
3 This is correct, but the
certification system there isn't properly established, so it
can be a debt.
It'll be okay.
Just keep an eye on the certification system and the book, and
get ESD certification. What does the state do? It's
not a single species review, right? Is
ESD certification a good thing? I'm
not saying that ROI is always good, but just
because it's well-certified doesn't mean it's a good song.
Anyway,
thank you for watching today. I'll kill you again next week.
I'll
post a poll on the YouTube community
to see if I can achieve it on Saturday.
Yes, I'll go with the 3-loss option.
Um,
if you're more comfortable with the left or have a
preference, please vote. Yes, I
'll turn it on again next week.
Please press it once even if it's tight.
Thank you for watching.